{
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "Which basketball player has won the most rings?",
      "options": [
        "Michael Jordan",
        "Stephen Curry",
        "Bill Russell",
        "Kareem Abdul-Jabbar"
      ],
      "correctOption": 2,
      "points": 5
    },
    {
      "question": "Which basketball player has the most all-time career nba points scored?",
      "options": [
        "Wilt Chamberlain",
        "Karl Malone",
        "Kareem Abdul-Jabbar",
        "LeBron James"
      ],
      "correctOption": 3,
      "points": 5
    },
    {
      "question": "Which basketball player earned the title of youngest mvp in nba history?",
      "options": [
        "Stephen Curry",
        "Derrick Rose",
        "Michael Jordan",
        "LeBron James"
      ],
      "correctOption": 1,
      "points": 5
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is the leader in percentage effectiveness of 3-point shots?",
      "options": ["Steve Kerr", "Stephen Curry", "Ray Allen", "Reggie Miller"],
      "correctOption": 0,
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the best statistic for winning/losing games in the single regular season?",
      "options": ["72/10", "73/9", "80/2", "70/12"],
      "correctOption": 1,
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is the most famous #1 draft pick and has won at least 1 mvp title?",
      "options": [
        "Michael Jordan",
        "Kobe Bryant",
        "Allen Iverson",
        "Zion Williamson"
      ],
      "correctOption": 2,
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "Which team is Blake Griffin playing for in 2023?",
      "options": [
        "Boston Celtics",
        "New York Nicks",
        "Brooklyn Nets",
        "LA Clippers"
      ],
      "correctOption": 0,
      "points": 20
    },
    {
      "question": "Which basketball player has never won a dunk contest?",
      "options": [
        "LeBron James",
        "Michael Jordan",
        "Zach Lavine",
        "Dwight Howard"
      ],
      "correctOption": 0,
      "points": 20
    },
    {
      "question": "Which basketball player made more than 30 rebounds in one game?",
      "options": [
        "Dwight Howard",
        "Draymond Green",
        "Dennis Rodman",
        "Shaquille O'Neal"
      ],
      "correctOption": 2,
      "points": 20
    },
    {
      "question": "Which NBA team retired Michael Jordan's jersey number despite the fact that he never played on it?",
      "options": [
        "Miami Heat",
        "Charlotte Hornets",
        "Washington Wizards",
        "None"
      ],
      "correctOption": 0,
      "points": 30
    }
  ]
}
